SELECT EFFECT  //  OMARCHY
▶ ROTATE ALL
RANDOM
SYNTH GRID
LASER ETCH
MATRIX RAIN
VHS DISTORTION
THUNDERSTORM
↑/↓ NAVIGATE    ENTER SELECT
ROTATE ALL
▶ RANDOM
SYNTH GRID
LASER ETCH
MATRIX RAIN
VHS DISTORTION
THUNDERSTORM
ROTATE ALL
RANDOM
▶ SYNTH GRID
LASER ETCH
MATRIX RAIN
VHS DISTORTION
THUNDERSTORM
SELECTED  //  SYNTH GRID
NEON OVERDRIVE
AN OMARCHY SCREENSAVER
NIGHT CITY NODE 13
IDLE, SHIFTED INTO OVERDRIVE.
01 // SYNTH GRID
EFFECT 01 / 05
02 // LASER ETCH
EFFECT 02 / 05
03 // MATRIX RAIN
EFFECT 03 / 05
04 // VHS DISTORTION
EFFECT 04 / 05
05 // THUNDERSTORM
EFFECT 05 / 05
PLAY MUSIC.
AUDIO LINK // LIVE
THE CITY LISTENS.
LASER ETCH // REPRISE
COOLING SPARKS // LIVE
NEON OVERDRIVE
FOR OMARCHY
5 EFFECTS  •  MUSIC-REACTIVE  •  MULTI-MONITOR
TRY IT  •  SHARE FEEDBACK
github.com/0xsl0th/omarchy-neon-overdrive-screensaver